ladies and gentlemen welcome
女士们先生们 你们好
my name is Walker Skype with Palo Alto education
我是来自Palo Alto Education的Walker Stipe
and today we had a treat for you
今天我们为你带来一个惊喜
we are going to be finding Larry
我们将会发现拉里
that's right we're gonna be finding Larry
对的，我们会找到拉里
where's Larry？well apparently he's right here
拉里在哪里呢？显然他就在这里
as you can see on the screen
正如你在屏幕上看到
this is Larry David he's one of the creators of Seinfeld
这是拉里·大卫 他是宋飞正传的创作者之一
which is a superb television show
宋飞正传是一部非常出色的电视剧
that is very funny and heartwarming
非常有趣和感人
but more importantly we are going to be
但更重要的是我们将要
doing some machine learning to find an object in a picture
做一些机器学习  来找到一个图片中的对象
today this object will be Larry I'm gonna find the Larry
今天这个对象将是拉里 我会找到拉里
our Larry will not look like this Larry
我们的拉里看起来不像这个拉里
will be a cartoon character ummm so so
而是一个卡通人物我是如此
briefly this is this is a harder project than we've done thus far
简而言之，这是项目比我们之前做的都要难一些
not only in scratches are quite a few more steps
不仅仅在scratch里有更多的步骤
but there is a certain level of difficulty
并且有一定的困难
when we're given a problem
当我们遇到一个难题时
for instance we've done things such as
例如我们已经完成了诸如
determining whether this face
确定这个区域图像是否
is your face or your dog's face or not your face
是你的脸或你的狗的脸或不是你的脸
right we're trying to say this is or
对  我们试图说这是或
isn't a face but we've been given a face
不是一张脸  在我们已经得到了一张脸的情况下
we know that and if we haven't then
我们知道  如果我们没有找到脸  那么
we just know that it's obviously not the
我们只知道  它显然不是
face we're looking for because at least
我们正在寻找的脸  因为至少
we're looking for a face this is hey
我们正在寻找一张脸  嘿
we're looking for Larry in a picture so
我们在图片中寻找拉里 所以
there could be tons of different things
这儿可能会有很多不同的东西
you have to like find where he is and
你必须要找到他所在的地方
then oh yeah he's right here
然后 噢 他就在这里
and then you determine if that's him so
然后你确定那是否是他
buckle up we're gonna do this
做好准备  我们就要开启今天的任务了
it's gonna be amazing
这简直太棒了
you got this we got this let's hop it
既然我们都准备好了  我们开始吧
though the first step that we would like
第一步我们将要
to accomplish is to get our uh a guide
要完成的是为我们找到一位向导
When we get a guide you can
当我们找到向导后  你就可以
follow on so you want to go into a
跟随着他了  所以你想进入一个
web browser some internet access methods
网页浏览器 一些互联网访问方法
we can get to the get to the Internet
我们就可以上网了
yep then we want to go to
是的  那么我们想要进入
machinelearningforkids.UK the the
“machinelearningforkids.UK”这个网页时
this guy right here I do this every time
这个家伙就在我鼠标点击的地方  我每次都这样做
you want to go here you can also just type in
如果你想要进入这个网页  你也可以输入
machinelearningforkids and
“machinelearningforkids”
you'll find it should be the first item there
你就会发现它  它应该就是网页上的第一条
so you wanna go in here you want to log in
所以你想要进入这个网页  想要登录进去
then you want to go to your worksheets
然后你想去你的工作表
right these are our worksheets and we are looking
这些就是我们的工作表  我们正在查看
notice how far down we have to go huh
我们还要学习那些内容
see this is intermediate also known
看这个  中级  你也可以理解为
as buckle up it's the law but also just
系好安全带  这是法律所要求的  但也为了公正
for your for your safety and for your
为了你的安全和你
own well-being just know this this could
自己的幸福  知道这个可以
be a little bit more involved more
让你有更多的参与
detailed then things we've done prior
更详细的  相对我们之前完成的工作而言
we shall rise to the challenge
我们更应该迎接挑战
so we're gonna go to our download project
所以我们会前往我们的下载项目
worksheet and we shall see this yeah so
即工作表  我们会看到这样的
we're here want to move down
就是在这啦  往下移动
and this this is kind of our stage
这是我们的网页
which we get to more in depth a little bit later
我们稍后会更深入学习
but as we see there are many characters
但正如我们看到的  这里有许多人物
we had a starfish we have a dinosaur
有一只海星  有一只恐龙
we get a bear we get a ballerina
有一只熊  一个芭蕾舞演员
we got all these people right they actually
以及所有的这些人  他们实际上
don't have names yet you have to decide
没有名字  但你必须决定
who is gonna be Larry
谁会成为拉里谁是
who's gonna be Larry it's it's naming time
谁会是拉里  这是我们的命名时间
I don't know it's exciting yeah so pick pick one of these guys
我也不知道谁是  真实太令人兴奋了 所以挑选其中之一
and determine them in your mind
并在你的心中确定一位
this is Larry I chose this dude
这是拉里  我选择了这个家伙
I just I thought they were so cute
我只是觉得他们太可爱了
so that's that's a Larry for this presentation
所以我就选了那个家伙作为此次演示的拉里
but in this worksheet
但在这张工作表中
they actually use the cat
他们实际上选用的是这只猫
notice scratch cat for the Larry
注意到了吗 这只scratch小猫
but my Larry is this cute little guy right here alright
但我的拉里是这只可爱的小家伙 就在这里
so you know pick one of those do it and
所以你只要选择其中作为你的拉里
then we are gonna hop on over to where
那么我们会进入一个
the magic happens which is this website
网站  那里正是奇迹发生的地方
machinimaforkids um
而这个网站呢  正是machinimaforkids
make sure logged in then we're gonna
确定登录后  然后我们会
create a project this little guy right there
创建一个项目  就在这儿的这个小家伙
boom smash that button
轰~ 撞击那个按钮
and we should see options such as this which
然后我们应该会看到这样的选项
if you've done projects before it's all very familiar
如果你之前完成过一些项目  那么你会对它感到非常熟悉
I don't really recommend this project
但我真心不推荐把这个项目
as your first project
作为你的第一个项目
although if you were brave if you're feeling it
不过如果你感觉自己非常勇敢的话  如果你非常感兴趣
do it anyway mmm be strong
那么就放手做吧 - 但是请一定坚强
yes to do that we're locating Larry
是的  我们正在寻找拉里
here whatever you want though recognizing images that part is important
你想通过图像识别做的任何事情这部分是很重要的
once you do this you know pop back
一旦你要做这个就(pop back 口误)
oh no pop in click it that's what you do
噢 不是 是点击它  这是你要做的
and you see all these these selections here
你会看到所有选择
such as these selections here
比如这里的这些选择
then you're gonna go to Train alright
然后你就进入train（训练）这个模块
a little little bit of ahead of myself don't hear right now
我刚刚讲得有点点快 网页还没显示
but we're gonna do it anyway
不管怎样  我们还是会做
it's fine okay though it is taking a long time to load
一切都正常，尽管这需要很长时间加载
so what we're gonna do is that we're
加载，所以我们要做的就是我们
gonna make two labels with this button right here
要用这个按钮在这里做两个标签
these are our two classes
这是我们的两个类
or two buckets of stuff but we're gonna
或两个桶  但我们会
put our pictures of Larry
把我们的拉里
and all the things that are not Larry
和所有不是拉里的照片放进去
now this may seem very similar
这些可能起来非常相似
and is to other projects we've done so far
我们迄今为止所做的其他项目可能也有点类似
except this one is kind of interesting
除了这个项目 它是非常有趣的  因为它
because it does it over not just an image
因为他运行的不仅仅是一个图像
but full image where what we're looking for is only in part of them
而是整幅图片  而在图片里我们寻找的只是其中一部分
if that makes sense
希望这样能说得通
we'll see we'll see more but basically
我们会看到  我们会看到更多  但基本上
you have boxes think of like a chess board
就像你有一些盒子  比如像国际象棋的棋盘
and typically what we've been doing
通常我们一直在做的
has only been looking at like
只是在寻找例如
one piece of the checker board
棋盘中的一小块格子
but now we're looking at the whole checker board and
但现在我们看到的是整个棋盘
Larry can only be in one of them
而拉里只是其中一小部分
so we can have to look through all of them and
所以我们可以把这些都先过一遍
make sure we don't classify we don't say
确保我们不分类  我们不会说
like oh yes the the starfish is Larry
诸如 噢 是的 海星是拉里这样的话
because the starfish is not Larry
因为海星不是拉里
the starfish is Patrick as we all know
我们都知道海星叫派大星
spongebob reference for
参考海绵宝宝这部动画片
all you folks out there alright so we do that
所有的人都在那里了  所以我们
we add those labels we don't actually
增加这些标签  实际上我们并没有
add the images at the end of the moment
在最后一刻添加这些图像
but we do that and we go back to
但我们这样做并且回到
a project which we'll do right here so I go back
这个项目  就在页面  所以我回到
project we are going to go over to Mr.scratch
项目  我们要点击scratch
ever gonna go to Mr. scratch and
继续点击scratch
we pop in each load actually not gonna
在加载中会弹出  但事实上我并不
use this one because I already have it open right here
使用这个  因为我已经在这里打开这个页面了
wooo map hacks so we do that
哈哈 全图出来啦  所以我们已经完成这一步啦
and we see things actually don't see
我们看了  事实上我们还没有看到
things which is why we need to open the
这就是为什么我们需要打开这个
project template click this guy you want
project template（项目模板） 点击这个链接
to open locate Larry cuz we're
打开locate Larry（找到拉里）这个链接  因为我们
looking for Larry to do the coding the scratch
正在寻找拉里  去完成这个编码 这个编程
scratch coding and so we've opened
编程代码  所以我们已经打开了
our project template we should hopefully
我们的项目模板  我们应该 希望
hopefully see something similar too looking what we see here
希望能看到我们这里所看到的一样
that is peruse the words
这是细读的一些文字
we have all these little boxes for
我们拥有所有这些小盒子
instance we got our scratched cats
例如  我们有scratch猫
we got our crab get the adorable horse oh
有我们的螃蟹  有可爱的马 噢
the gang's all here and then we have all
这整个团队都在这里  然后其他的
these other areas which are basically
区域则是一些基本的元素  诸如
the quadrants the sections the cubes the
这儿有象限  栏目  立方体以及
boxes of our picture right there
我们的图片框
like little areas in it there's 12 of them
他们就像一些小区域  一共有12个构成
and these are those stuff they're also up here
这些也是其中一部分  他们也会出现在这儿
but these are the connected right
但这些都是相关联的
all right so first what we're
所以  首先  我们
gonna do is go to the store hit part of our first quadrants
要去的是我们右侧“store hit”的部分
this is our first guy
这是我们的第一个家伙
zero zero dude and we look at these define store hit
编号为00  我们看下这些定义储存的点击
cuz when we see Larry
因为当我们看到拉里时
you want to make sure that we remember
你会想确认我们记住
that we saw Larry so we're
我们看到拉里了  所以我们
gonna go there and we're going to make some adjustments
要去那里  我们要去做一些调整
they're fairly simple
相当简单
but as we shall see in a moment
但正如我们等会儿会看到
they may take some time
它可能会需要一些时间
hey just just bear with me so these are
嘿  和我一起吧  这些只是
these are simple just drag drop things
只是简单的拖放东西
you want to do that for the define hit
为了想要做到定义 hit 函数
then you'd like to do the same exact thing
那么你也要做同样的事情
except when you were looking for misses things that are not Larry
除非你正在寻找不是拉里的东西
perhaps we're looking for things that are not Larry
也许我们正在寻找的东西不是拉里
interesting
真实有趣呢
so I believe that is the only um difference between those two adjustments there
所以我相信这是两个调整中的唯一的差别
okay so it's possible
好吧  这是可能的
it's possible that um you know
这是可能的  你知道
hey do this thing for this guy and this guy
嘿  为这家伙还有他
and this guy and there's 12 yes
和他  这里一共有12位 是的
you gotta do this 12 times
你需要做12次
but what a great opportunity to read a book  am i right
阅读一本书是多么棒的机会  我说的对吗
I like reading books particularly an audio book
我特别喜欢看书  尤其是以音频的方式听书
because then your eyes can do these things
因为那时你就可以做这些事情了
so it takes a while
所以还需要一段时间
this is the one of the mill of this portion of the of the video
这是视频运作的一部分
but it's it's fine
但它其实还好
just drag drop it is a copy paste function
只是拖放  它是一个复制粘贴功能
I couldn't find it if you can find it
我没能找到它  如果你能找到
please tell your friends and share with your family
请告诉你的朋友并与你的家人分享
and I'll celebrate because it'll save a lot of time
我会为你庆祝  因为它会节约你很多时间
I could not so I just did it by hand
我没有做到  所以我手动这样做了
forgot to save lost it
忘记保存  丢失
we did it and then at that point I remember to save
我们曾经经历过  在那个时候我记得我保存了
I saved very fervently quite often
我经常按保存键
alright so you're gonna do that for each of them
好吧  所以你会为他们每个都做保存
you got this
记住了吗？
do not despair all right we do this next
不要绝望  好嘛  我们接下来会做这件事
we move on to the next stage alright so
我们进入到下一个页面
I click on the stage and I named mine Larry
我点击了页面  并命名为我的拉里
I'd like Larry
我喜欢拉里
Larry was a great name its name of this video
拉里是一个很棒的名字  它也是这个视频的名字
you can name it whatever you want
你可以将它命名为任何你想要的东西
he named yours Patrick
比如命名为你的派大星
trying to come up with a name I can do that
尝试着想出一个名字  我可以
you can name it whatever you want
你也可以命名为任何你想要的
but make sure that you computer knows
但要确保你的电脑知道
that you're looking for that name right
你在寻找这个名字
because that's it's learning to look for something
因为“寻找某物”的学习
needs to know what this is what
需要知道这是什么
so I wanted to click on stage in the top right
所以我想要点击右页面的右上方
this little bity name box right there
就是这儿的这个极小的名字框框
I'm just trying to make sure they're exactly the same
我只是在试图确认它们完全一样
such as capitalization
比如大写字母
and things of like now we're going to train
以及类似的一些细节  现在我们要训练啦
we're gonna collect some data
我们会收集一些数据
so as we see here we can click the train button
所以正如我们所看到的  我们可以点击train（训练）这个按钮
which is what we're doing and it may take a moment
这是我们正在做的事情  这可能需要一点时间
but it's going to set up the stage
但它会建立这个窗口
and it will ask you
它会问你
this this little portion right here will pop up
这一框框会出现在这里
and you're going to want to click on your character
并且你将要点击
and nothing else
其他什么都不用做
make sure that you click on your dude
只要确保你点击你要选择的对象
as mentioned I picked a little Pico
正如上面提到的  我选了一个小小Pico
his name is Pico this little guy who's your toughest head right here
他的名字是Pico  这个小家伙是你要攻克的难题
but that is the guy
但就是这个家伙
and then briefly after that
然后在那之后
it will take a moment and it will ask you
过一小会儿 它会要求你
to click on somewhere other than Larry
点击在除了拉里之外的其他区域
or whoever you named your little guy as do so
或除了你命名的小家伙的之外的区域
literally anywhere else doesn't matter
简单地说  点击其他任何地方都可以
but don't click on your dude
但不要点击你选的家伙
if you did this incorrectly if Oh I intended
如果你没有正确点击 噢 天啊
I intended to click on Larry
我打算点击拉里
but I clicked on the horse or the bear or the moon
但我意外点击了马 或熊 或月亮
because one of the pictures is the moon
因为其中一张照片就是月亮
so do that and that's ok it's ok because we
这样做也是没关系的  因为我们
will go back to our project
会回到我们的项目
so briefly you want to make sure
所以简单地说你想确保
you have at least ten of these uh these photos in each side right
每一次至少要有十个这样的照片
so a run should gather you a data point for each side
所以每一次运行应该收集一个数据点
occasionally it doesn't take
偶尔它不会获得
it just doesn't store it or I just can't count
比如它没有存储  或者只是因为我不能计算
also very possible
这也是很有可能的
but so make sure that you have at least ten
但请确保你至少有十个
in your training set in each of your boxes and
在你每个训练集里
make sure that they are correct right
确保它们正确无误
so if Larry is in your non-Larry section
所以如果拉里在你的非拉里部分
get them out of there there
让他们离开那儿
you are Larry your Larry
你是拉里  你的拉里
if you've any non-Larry photos in the Larry section
如果你有任何非拉里的照片
well that is of course incorrect
当然是不正确的
because Larry is Larry and not Hernan
因为拉里就是拉里  而不是埃尔南之类的
okay you get it just check there
好的  你已经理解了 只要检查一下
and that is as you see I'm gonna go back to your profile
就像你看到的  我要点击“back to project”（回到项目）的按钮
I will just show you
我会演示给你看的
I'll just we'll just hop in right all right
我会  我们将会进入这个页面
so projects oh no that's the wrong one I missed up face lock locate Larry
项目 噢不 不是这个 我错过了 这是面部识别 这是定位拉里
and in your training data we can see the data
在你的训练数据里我们可以看到这些数据
as it loads yes
当它加载完后
so here we see we have actually twelve and thirteen
所以在这里  我们看到我们其实已经有十二和十三个了
so many images oh my goodness do you see this
这么多图像 噢 我的天啊！你看到这个了吗？
this actually is interesting
这实际上很有趣
I did this a moment ago unbeknownst to myself
我刚刚做了什么  我自己都没知道到
we see I'm sorry but a horse is simply not Larry
我很抱歉  但马显然不是拉里
so we shall take that out of our data set of things that are Larry
因此 我们应该把他从我们与拉里有关的数据集里移除
this is good
这边没有错误
and then on the right we see that Larry
然后在右边  我们看到的拉里
our little peeko guy is nowhere to be found
我们的小家伙并没有出现在这儿
just as we want yes
就像我们想要的一样
ladies and gentlemen I hope you're ready
女士们  先生们  我希望你们准备好了
because it is time for some magic
因为魔术时间来临了
it's time to do the machine learning magic present time
该是我们进行机器学习的魔术展示的时刻了
we're gonna do the training
我们要去训练了
we're gonna do the training the model now
我们现在要去训练模型
it's gonna click learn & test button
点击“learn & test”（学习&测试）的按钮
once we have done so
这样做了之后
we will scroll to the bottom of the screen
滚动页面至屏幕底部
we'll see things that are different from what we see here
就会看到与我们现在看到的不同的界面
and that's okay
这没关系
because this is what you should see after you press the button
因为这是你按下按钮后看到的界面
and wait awhile
并等待一小会儿
and it might be a while
也可能是一段时间
because images are big and they're messy and
因为图像很大  而且他们很乱并且
computers have a hard time with them basically
电脑处理他们并不是那么容易
which is why we're doing this these stuff
这就是我们为什么要这样做的原因
cuz we do that and it is trained
我们这样做就是要训练它
and now we have a model which means we
现在我们有一个模型  这意味着我们
can go on to the next portion
可以继续我们的下一部分
we're gonna go back into scratch
我们将会从头开始
back to scratch back to reality and
回到最初的状态  回到现实
we are gonna change some things around right
我们要改变一些东西
so what we're changing it's different
所以我们要改变的是什么呢？有点不同
same with all we've changed before right
于我们之前做的改变
we're gonna keep keep all that stuff added earlier
保持先前添加的所有内容
hopefully you save your project
希望你保存了你的的项目
don'tforget don't forget I would know
不要忘记  不要忘记  我知道有人忘记了
so sad it's okay um we're gonna change these guys out here
太悲伤了  没关系  我们接下来会改变这些家伙
which if you notice
如果你注意到了
we need to scroll down if you're like
我们需要向下滚动 如果你发现
I can't find it it's because it's probably not on the screen
你找不到它  那可能是因为它不在屏幕上
you need to scroll down
你需要滚动屏幕
so you do so find it down here and
往下拉之后  你就能在这里找到它啦
you change the stuff right it is the stuff right there
改变这玩意儿  就是这些
do not neglect do take note
不要忽视他们  请注意
but the difference is in words here
区别在于这些文字
highly recommend following along with those words
强烈建议照着这些文字
another thing of note that
另一件需要注意的事是
you don't want to neglect is scroll scroll alright
不要忽视的是... 往下 往下
as we see here it's got a top and it's got a bottom
正如我们在这里看到广播功能 顶部(接受) 底部(发布)
they're different which is okay
并且他们是不同的  这没有关系
in fact they can be so different
事实上他们可以截然不同
this guy's got a top doesn't even have a bottom
这家伙有顶部(接受)但却没有一个底部(发送)
it's totally okay it's totally fine
这完全没问题  好吗  这是完全可以的
it's how it's designed
它就长这样
and it should work that's okay alright
这没有影响  是可以的
so we do so for all 12 up again
所以我们做 是为了让12个再次测试
get a good book pop on a movie just think just sit there and
拿一本好书 一部流行电影上  或沉思 或静坐
enjoy the enjoy the silence or the noise in the background
享受沉默或是背景乐的喧嚣
whichever but it's gonna take a while
无论哪种方式  但它会需要一段时间
have to do for all 12 but it's okay
因为所有的12个都需要测试  但这没关系
once you have done so don't forget to save
一旦你完成了  别忘了保存
please don't forget to save do it for me
请千万不要忘记保存  为了我保存吧
do it for me don't forget to save
为我做到这一点  不要忘记保存
you're going to want to test it it's time
是时候你要测试它了
please jump it's time we've made it
让我们欢呼跳跃吧  我们成功了
or maybe right to find out
或者我们至少能确认
what we've made at least to the point
至少我们所做的已经到了我们可以说
we can tell we've made made it right yeah alright
我们已经做到了 啊 就是这样
so we are gonna click the start button the flag
所以我们要点击“start”（开始）按钮 也就是这个旗帜
we're setting it up we're setting it up
我们正在建立  正在建立
the green flag by the way
顺便提一下  这个绿色旗子
if it's taking a long time is a great way
如果你等了要很长时间  点击绿色旗子是一个好方法
to do exactly that because sometimes
去加快速度  因为有时
it just kind of freezes up and that's fine
页面会卡住  这没关系
so it's gonna pop up in a moment
所以它会在一会儿之后弹出或
or it won't and we'll click the green flag and
也可能不会  然后我们点击绿色标志
that'll be that
就是那个
I think we might click the green flag we are gonna click the green flag
我想我们可以再点击那里的绿色标志
yeah we are you do this and
是的  我们正在这么做 你也需要
we are gonna see how well it does now
我们会看到  现在效果如何呢
I'll tell you right now
我现在告诉你
it doesn't do a great job of putting the like little arrow things
对于摆放像小箭头这样的东西  它做得不是很好
it makes like okay
这显得... 好像
you see Larry's right here we have found him
你看拉里就在这里  我们已经找到他了
yes kind of puts him like a little bit off to the side
是的  他的位置有点偏一侧
but I have seen this over and over again
我看到好几次这样已经好多遍了
and I can tell that
并且我可以告诉大家
it's just it's just putting him off to the side
这只是让他偏离到了一边而已
but it knows that he should be
但又好像知道他应该
I think like pointing is the idea
我觉得可以指出他的位置是一个想法
these guys were taking a while
这些人需要较长的一段时间
I think we're just gonna let it go
我觉得我们就顺其自然吧
it's gonna do it it's gonna be so good
它会做到的  它会很好地完成
this is some really holly time we can
这真是神圣的时刻  我们可以
we can recognize the dancing that's going
我们可以认为他们在跳舞
here we go yes we would like to test
终于出现了  我们可以去测试了
you like to see if it's working
看看它是否能运行
all right let's get this guy all screen oh my goodness
好吧  他出现在了整个屏幕上  噢  我的天啊
is Larry there is he
是拉里在那里吗  是他吗？
yes so as mentioned before
噢 是的 正如之前提到的
it doesn't do a great job of like putting putting a little
他做得并不是非常出色
like is Larry here like very ac
就像拉里的一部分
accurately it's like (balabala)
准确地说，它就像(没听清)
but if you take my word for it I have played this game
但如果你能认同我的话  这个游戏我已经玩了很多遍
enough to know that like that
足以知道
configuration the way those things are set up
这样的位置摆设  这些东西建立的方式
it can tell that he's there
它可以指明他在那里
it's actually it's actually working
实际上 它实际上能够运作
we're gonna run another one even though
尽管如此 我们仍然会运行另一个
it will take a while that's alright
这将需要等候一段时间  没关系
maybe it just goes faster if it's not full screen
也许它只是更快，如果它不是全屏的话
this is possible yeah okay
这是非常有可能的 哇 可以了！
good to know it goes a lot quicker if it's not full screen
太开心了  如果不是全屏的话加载速度会快很多
sure and we see
是吧  我们看到
that Larry is I'm just gonna guess
拉里在...  我猜测
he's like something here is
他可能会在这儿
see look at this look at this
看  看这个哦  看看这个
oh come on that's pretty cool we have an image
噢  这也太酷了吧  我们有一个图像有一个
there's a bunch of stuff going on we can tell that
这儿有一堆东西出现了  我们知道
Larry is there even though we got these
拉里就在这儿  尽管我们
little these little boring things over his face
看到了一些无聊的东西挡在他的脸上
there he is hey Larry
他在那儿  嘿  拉里
yeah so how is that we made a thing
是的  我们做了一个程序
that can find our guy we can
可以找到我们选定的家伙  我们可以
we can find him pick him out of a crowd amazing
我们可以找到他 把他从人群中挑出来  太神奇了
so let's say perhaps yours didn't work
我们假设  可能你的并没有成功
it just didn't work there was something wrong
他就是没有成功  一定是哪里有问题
Oh Shutts follow the law
真是讨厌  遵循了规则
I did all the steps for each 12 of those boxes might I add
我添加了12个盒子  并为他们做了一切步骤
I even remember to save it
我我甚至记得保​​存了
it still doesn't work something is awry
它仍然无法正常工作  一定是哪里出错了
something is amiss it don't function
一些步骤有缺陷  以致它不起作用
it's okay this is part of the learning process
没关系  这就是学习过程的一部分
which maybe not enjoy
你可能不喜欢的这个过程
but it's still really helpful
但它还是非常有帮助的  每个人都还是很有帮助的
yay whatever one wants to hear sound like Calvin's dad
人们想要听到的不过是像加尔文的爸爸所说的
if you've ever read Calvin and Hobbes
如果你读过卡尔文和霍布斯是
it's awesome highly recommend oh yeah
那真是太棒了  强烈推荐哦
here we there are some options okay
这儿有一些选项
could be unlike the machine learning side
可能不像机器学习
right where you didn't have enough data
你没有足够的数据
even though you already had 10 it
尽管你已经有10个了
just wasn't enough more typically better
只是不够多  通常多一点更好
maybe your data was messy
也许你的数据很混乱
maybe there's some noise in your data as they say ak8
或许你的数据中会出现一些噪音  例如他们会说ak8
it's another way of saying that you had the horse
这是说  你有这匹马
as just like I did
就像我所做的那样
I put the horse I called the I called the horse Larry
我把马加了进去  我把马取名为拉里
and it won't help the horse
当然这也不会对识别这匹马有多大帮助
the horse I'm not Larry no man
那马说我不是拉里  才不是呢
my name is Joe Joe the horse do
我的名字是乔  乔是这匹马  你检查
you check your your data and the training and
你检查你的数据 并训练
tests or the train part
以及测试  或者训练部分
it shows all you little pictures if you're looking at
那显示你所有的照片 如果你正在看
that's another thing check
检查是另一件事  同时
and also the the code there's a lot of code
同时代码  这里有很多代码
we adjusted right
我们调整了很多对吗
there's a lot of something that we're messing around with
我们搞乱好些东西
any part of that could you know just oh
你可以知道的
I put Larry and not Larry and
我把拉里和非拉里搞混
now everything is broken and nothing works
现在一切都被打破  没有任何一部分是可行的
so feel free to check in there
所以你随时检查  可能会采取
may take some time but it's okay it's fine
可能会花费一段时间  但没关系  这是允许的
we shall prevail
我们一定会获胜的
yes so what what did we do here
所以我们在做什么呢
we made a super cool little finding Larry box thing
一个超酷发现拉里的小盒子
right we trained it on some things
对吧  我们训练它执行
that are Larry right we saw the images
寻找拉里的任务  我们看到了这些图像
and meet and tell that's Larry
并会辨别那就是拉里
that's our little pico so I picked a pico
就是我们的小Piko  所以我选了pico
oh he's adorable
噢  他实在太可爱了
but you can pick who you want so we
但你可以你想要的任何一个  所以我们
do that and then give it a new image
做到这一点后  然后给它一个新的形象
which which are which has things a little bit changed around
这些形象 会有一些细微的变化
you notice that
你应该注意到了
but the characters will be in different positions
那个角色会出现在不同的位置
they'll be a little bit different sized
他们的大小也会发生微妙的变化
and the backdrop
以及背景
will be different occasion
也会变成不同的场合将是
will be on the moon which I really enjoyed
可能会在月亮下  这是我非常喜欢的景色
and then we can tell where there Larry is
然后我们可以知道拉里在哪里了
even though things have changed you know
尽管事情已经改变了
we haven't just memorized we have generalized
我们不仅仅记住了 我们已经推广了
which is another way of
也就是说
saying we're pretty good at the game
我们非常擅长这个游戏了
right good at the game
非常擅长这个游戏
the game of finding Larry we're pretty good at it
一场关于发现拉里的游戏 我们很擅长
yeah so that's that's what we've done here
是的  这就是我们在这里所做的
is be able to find Larry in an image of other creatures
能够在一副有着众多动物的图像中找到拉里
amazing
真的太令人震惊了
once again ladies and gentlemen
女士们 先生们 容我再次介绍下自己
this is Walker Stipe with Palo Alto education
我是来自Palo Alto Education的Walker Stipe
wishing you a very very wonderful day
祝你度过精彩美好的一天
thank you
谢谢